Viewers all over the world, listen to me.
Hear the voice of God.
Your heart is the man himself.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
The heart is so important because it must be at its best for God.
For your heart to be at its best for God, it must be spiritual.
Our heart is the prayer room, temple of God, contact,
communication point, landing point for the Holy Ghost.
Where is your heart -
full of unforgiveness, bitterness, pain of the past, bad feelings towards others?
That root in your heart that caused you unforgiveness, bitterness,
bad feelings towards others - be terminated, in the name of Jesus!
Receive a free heart - a heart without bitterness,
a heart without unforgiveness,
a heart without bad feelings,
a heart without pain of the past, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Receive!
Be free!
In the name of Jesus!
Viewers, you need a free heart to follow Jesus.
I have decided to follow Jesus
No turning back
Only a free heart, a free spirit can follow Jesus.
For your heart to be free, it must be spiritual
because the Spirit of God expresses Himself through our hearts.
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, begin to see yourself the way Jesus sees you.
Jesus sees you as a person without affliction, stagnation, poverty.
Begin to see yourself the way Jesus sees you.
Oh Holy Spirit, locate me in Your mercy and deliver me, in the name of Jesus.
Locate me in Your mercy.
Viewers all over the world, open your lips.
Locate me in Your mercy and deliver me, in the name of Jesus!
Deliver me, in the name of Jesus!
Free me, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips.
Locate me in Your mercy.
Oh Holy Spirit, locate me in Your mercy.
Oh Holy Spirit, locate me in Your mercy and deliver me, in the name of Jesus.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Anonymous
RV: Mel Flowers 31/12/2018